{
  "easy": [
    { "problem": "11 × 21", "answer": 231, "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/easy/11x21_sol.gif"},
    { "problem": "11 × 32", "answer": 352, "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/easy/11x32_sol.gif"},
    { "problem": "11 × 43", "answer": 473, "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/easy/11x43_sol.gif"},
    { "problem": "11 × 54", "answer": 594, "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/easy/11x54_sol.gif"},
    { "problem": "11 × 13", "answer": 143, "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/easy/11x13_sol.gif"},
    { "problem": "11 × 15", "answer": 165, "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/easy/11x15_sol.gif"},
    { "problem": "11 × 81", "answer": 891, "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/easy/11x81_sol.gif"},
    { "problem": "11 × 10", "answer": 110, "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/easy/11x10_sol.gif"},
    { "problem": "11 × 11", "answer": 121, "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/easy/11x11_sol.gif"},
    { "problem": "11 × 20", "answer": 220, "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/easy/11x20_sol.gif"}
  ],
  "medium": [
    { "problem": "11 × 29", "answer": 319, "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/medium/11x29_sol.gif"},
    { "problem": "11 × 38", "answer": 418, "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/medium/11x38_sol.gif"},
    { "problem": "11 × 47", "answer": 517, "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/medium/11x47sol.gif"},
    { "problem": "11 × 56", "answer": 616, "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/medium/11x56_sol.gif"},
    { "problem": "11 × 39", "answer": 429, "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/medium/11x39_sol.gif"},
    { "problem": "11 × 48", "answer": 528, "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/medium/11x48_sol.gif"},
    { "problem": "11 × 59", "answer": 649, "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/medium/11x59_sol.gif"},
    { "problem": "11 × 67", "answer": 737, "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/medium/11x67_sol.gif"},
    { "problem": "11 × 75", "answer": 825, "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/medium/11x75_sol.gif"},
    { "problem": "11 × 89", "answer": 979, "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/medium/11x89_sol.gif"}
  ],
  "hard": [
    { "problem": "11 × 101", "answer": 1111, "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/hard/11x101_sol.gif"},
    { "problem": "11 × 121", "answer": 1331, "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/hard/11x121_sol.gif"},
    { "problem": "11 × 130", "answer": 1430, "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/hard/11x130_sol.gif"},
    { "problem": "11 × 145", "answer": 1595, "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/hard/11x145_sol.gif"},
    { "problem": "11 × 212", "answer": 2332, "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/hard/11x212_sol.gif"},
    { "problem": "11 × 303", "answer": 3333, "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/hard/11x303_sol.gif"},
    { "problem": "11 × 410", "answer": 4510, "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/hard/11x410_sol.gif"},
    { "problem": "11 × 111", "answer": 1221, "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/hard/11x111_sol.gif"},
    { "problem": "11 × 123", "answer": 1353, "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/hard/11x123_sol.gif"},
    { "problem": "11 × 231", "answer": 2541, "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/hard/11x231_sol.gif"}
  ],
  "test": [
    { "problem": "11 × 29", "answer": 319, "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/test/11x29_sol.gif",
      "id": 1},
    { "problem": "11 × 38", "answer": 418, "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/test/11x38_sol.gif",
      "id": 2},
    { "problem": "11 × 12", "answer": 132, "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/test/11x12_sol.gif",
      "id": 3},
    { "problem": "11 × 67", "answer": 737, "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/test/11x67_sol.gif",
      "id": 4},
    { "problem": "11 × 145", "answer": 1595, "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/test/11x145_sol.gif",
      "id": 5},
    { "problem": "11 × 21", "answer": 231, "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/test/11x21_sol.gif",
      "id": 6},
    { "problem": "11 × 56", "answer": 616, "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/test/11x56_sol.gif",
      "id": 7},
    { "problem": "11 × 303", "answer": 3333, "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/test/11x303_sol.gif",
      "id": 8},
    { "problem": "11 × 75", "answer": 825, "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/test/11x75_sol.gif",
      "id": 9},
    { "problem": "11 × 121", "answer": 1331, "solution_gif": "static/data/mult11gifs/test/11x121_sol.gif",
      "id": 10}
  ]
}
